[
    {
        "Question": "Q: 393 + 912",
        "Answer": "A: 1305",
        "Explanation": "300 + 900 = 1200\n90 + 10 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 932 + 435",
        "Answer": "A: 1367",
        "Explanation": "900 + 400 = 1300\n30 + 30 = 60\n2 + 5 = 7\n1300 + 60 = 1360\n1360 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 646 + 830",
        "Answer": "A: 1476",
        "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 878 + 770",
        "Answer": "A: 1648",
        "Explanation": "800 + 700 = 1500\n70 + 70 = 140\n1500 + 140 = 1640\n1640 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 732 + 504",
        "Answer": "A: 1236",
        "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n30 + 4 = 34\n1200 + 34 = 1234\n1234 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 405 + 136",
        "Answer": "A: 541",
        "Explanation": "400 + 100 = 500\n5 + 30 = 35\n500 + 35 = 535\n535 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 534 + 538",
        "Answer": "A: 1072",
        "Explanation": "500 + 500 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n4 + 8 = 12\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 219 + 334",
        "Answer": "A: 553",
        "Explanation": "200 + 300 = 500\n10 + 30 = 40\n500 + 40 = 540\n540 + 9 + 4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 446 + 372",
        "Answer": "A: 818",
        "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n40 + 70 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 6 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 863 + 628",
        "Answer": "A: 1491",
        "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 20 = 80\n1400 + 80 = 1480\n1480 + 3\n1483 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 670 + 909",
        "Answer": "A: 1579",
        "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n70 + 9 = 79\n1500 + 79"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 469 + 353",
        "Answer": "A: 822",
        "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n60 + 50 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 9 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 564 + 631",
        "Answer": "A: 1195",
        "Explanation": "500 + 600 = 1100\n60 + 30 = 90\n1100 + 90 = 1190\n1190 + 4 + 1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 815 + 422",
        "Answer": "A: 1237",
        "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n15 + 20 = 35\n1200 + 35 = 1235\n1235 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 388 + 722",
        "Answer": "A: 1110",
        "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n80 + 20 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 8 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 398 + 247",
        "Answer": "A: 645",
        "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 40 = 130\n500 + 130 = 630\n630 + 8\n638 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 570 + 766",
        "Answer": "A: 1336",
        "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n70 + 60 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 252 + 593",
        "Answer": "A: 845",
        "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n50 + 90 = 140\n700 + 140 = 840\n840 + 5 = 845\n845 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 648 + 482",
        "Answer": "A: 1130",
        "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n40 + 80 = 120\n1000 + 120 = 1120\n1120 + 8 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 267 + 572",
        "Answer": "A: 839",
        "Explanation": "200 + 500 = 700\n60 + 70 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 291 + 109",
        "Answer": "A: 400",
        "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n91 + 9 = 100\n300 + 100"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 145 + 222",
        "Answer": "A: 367",
        "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n40 + 20 = 60\n5 + 2 = 7\n300 + 60 = 360\n360 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 743 + 825",
        "Answer": "A: 1568",
        "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500\n40 + 20 = 60\n3 + 5 = 8\n1500 + 60 = 1560\n1560 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 747 + 731",
        "Answer": "A: 1478",
        "Explanation": "700 + 700 = 1400\n40 + 30 = 70\n1400 + 70 = 1470\n1470 + 7 + 1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 758 + 240",
        "Answer": "A: 998",
        "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900\n50 + 40 = 90\n900 + 90 = 990\n990 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 506 + 287",
        "Answer": "A: 793",
        "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n6 + 80 = 86\n700 + 86 = 786\n786 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 133 + 338",
        "Answer": "A: 471",
        "Explanation": "100 + 300 = 400\n30 + 30 = 60\n3 + 8 = 11\n400 + 60 = 460\n460 + 11"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 859 + 405",
        "Answer": "A: 1264",
        "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n50 + 0 = 50\n9 + 5 = 14\n1200 + 50 = 1250\n1250 + 14"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 273 + 873",
        "Answer": "A: 1146",
        "Explanation": "200 + 800 = 1000\n70 + 70 = 140\n3 + 3 = 6\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 943 + 779",
        "Answer": "A: 1722",
        "Explanation": "900 + 700 = 1600\n40 + 70 = 110\n1600 + 110 = 1710\n1710 + 3 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 189 + 550",
        "Answer": "A: 739",
        "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 50 = 130\n600 + 130 = 730\n730 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 998 + 560",
        "Answer": "A: 1558",
        "Explanation": "900 + 500 = 1400\n90 + 60 = 150\n1400 + 150 = 1550\n1550 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 822 + 226",
        "Answer": "A: 1048",
        "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n22 + 20 = 42\n1000 + 42 = 1042\n1042 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 603 + 805",
        "Answer": "A: 1408",
        "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n3 + 5 = 8\n1400 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 274 + 136",
        "Answer": "A: 410",
        "Explanation": "200 + 100 = 300\n70 + 30 = 100\n4 + 6 = 10\n300 + 100 = 400\n400 + 10"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 387 + 244",
        "Answer": "A: 631",
        "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n80 + 40 = 120\n500 + 120 = 620\n620 + 7 + 4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 953 + 225",
        "Answer": "A: 1178",
        "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100\n50 + 20 = 70\n1100 + 70 = 1170\n1170 + 3 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 261 + 437",
        "Answer": "A: 698",
        "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n60 + 30 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 220 + 946",
        "Answer": "A: 1166",
        "Explanation": "200 + 900 = 1100  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1100 + 60 = 1160  \n1160 + 6  "
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 321 + 707",
        "Answer": "A: 1028",
        "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n20 + 7 = 27\n1000 + 27 = 1027\n1027 + 1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 585 + 891",
        "Answer": "A: 1476",
        "Explanation": "500 + 800 = 1300\n80 + 10 = 90\n1300 + 90 = 1390\n1390 + 5\n1390 + 1\n139"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 414 + 553",
        "Answer": "A: 967",
        "Explanation": "400 + 500 = 900\n10 + 50 = 60\n900 + 60 = 960\n960 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 809 + 645",
        "Answer": "A: 1454",
        "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n9 + 40 = 49\n1400 + 49 = 1449\n1449 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 385 + 419",
        "Answer": "A: 804",
        "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n80 + 10 = 90\n700 + 90 = 790\n790 + 5 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 645 + 869",
        "Answer": "A: 1514",
        "Explanation": "600 + 800 = 1400\n40 + 60 = 100\n1400 + 100 = 1500\n1500 + 5 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 136 + 545",
        "Answer": "A: 681",
        "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600  \n30 + 40 = 70  \n600 + 70 = 670  \n670 + 6 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 888 + 446",
        "Answer": "A: 1334",
        "Explanation": "800 + 400 = 1200\n80 + 40 = 120\n8 + 6 = 14\n1200 + 120 = 1320\n1320 + 14"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 492 + 348",
        "Answer": "A: 840",
        "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n90 + 40 = 130\n700 + 130 = 830\n830 + 10 = 840\n840"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 203 + 290",
        "Answer": "A: 493",
        "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n3 + 90 = 93\n400 + 93 "
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 765 + 386",
        "Answer": "A: 1151",
        "Explanation": "700 + 300 = 1000\n60 + 80 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 5 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 818 + 828",
        "Answer": "A: 1646",
        "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600  \n18 + 20 = 38  \n1600 + 38 = 1638  \n1638 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 769 + 132",
        "Answer": "A: 901",
        "Explanation": "700 + 100 = 800\n60 + 30 = 90\n800 + 90 = 890\n890 + 9 = 899\n899 + 2"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 476 + 660",
        "Answer": "A: 1136",
        "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n70 + 60 = 130\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 146 + 401",
        "Answer": "A: 547",
        "Explanation": "100 + 400 = 500\n40 + 1 = 41\n500 + 41 = 541\n541 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 390 + 207",
        "Answer": "A: 597",
        "Explanation": "300 + 200 = 500\n90 + 7 = 97\n500 + 97"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 475 + 667",
        "Answer": "A: 1142",
        "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000  \n70 + 60 = 130  \n5 + 7 = 12  \n1000 + 130 = 1130  \n1130 + 12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 961 + 179",
        "Answer": "A: 1140",
        "Explanation": "900 + 100 = 1000\n60 + 70 = 130\n1 + 9 = 10\n1000 + 130 = 1130\n1130 + 10"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 593 + 229",
        "Answer": "A: 822",
        "Explanation": "500 + 200 = 700\n90 + 20 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 3\n813 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 154 + 182",
        "Answer": "A: 336",
        "Explanation": "150 + 180 = 330\n4 + 2 = 6\n330 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 836 + 104",
        "Answer": "A: 940",
        "Explanation": "800 + 100 = 900\n30 + 4 = 34\n900 + 34 = 934\n934 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 478 + 394",
        "Answer": "A: 872",
        "Explanation": "400 + 300 = 700\n70 + 90 = 160\n700 + 160 = 860\n860 + 8 + 4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 558 + 907",
        "Answer": "A: 1465",
        "Explanation": "500 + 900 = 1400\n50 + 7 = 57\n1400 + 57 = 1457\n1457 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 261 + 185",
        "Answer": "A: 446",
        "Explanation": "200 + 60 = 260\n260 + 1 = 261\n100 + 80 = 180\n180 + 5 = 185\n260 + 180 = 440\n"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 101 + 236",
        "Answer": "A: 337",
        "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n1 + 30 = 31\n300 + 31 = 331\n331 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 441 + 892",
        "Answer": "A: 1333",
        "Explanation": "400 + 800 = 1200\n40 + 90 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 249 + 434",
        "Answer": "A: 683",
        "Explanation": "200 + 400 = 600\n40 + 30 = 70\n9 + 4 = 13\n600 + 70 = 670\n670 + 13"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 658 + 245",
        "Answer": "A: 903",
        "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800  \n50 + 40 = 90  \n800 + 90 = 890  \n890 + 13"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 886 + 261",
        "Answer": "A: 1147",
        "Explanation": "800 + 200 = 1000\n80 + 60 = 140\n1000 + 140 = 1140\n1140 + 6 = 1146\n1146 +"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 335 + 431",
        "Answer": "A: 766",
        "Explanation": "300 + 400 = 700\n30 + 30 = 60\n700 + 60 = 760\n760 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 867 + 683",
        "Answer": "A: 1550",
        "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n60 + 80 = 140\n1400 + 140 = 1540\n1540 + 10"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 279 + 236",
        "Answer": "A: 515",
        "Explanation": "200 + 200 = 400\n70 + 30 = 100\n400 + 100 = 500\n9 + 6 = 15\n500 + 15"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 620 + 740",
        "Answer": "A: 1360",
        "Explanation": "600 + 700 = 1300  \n20 + 40 = 60  \n1300 + 60 = 1360  "
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 563 + 462",
        "Answer": "A: 1025",
        "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n60 + 60 = 120\n3 + 2 = 5\n900 + 120 = 1020\n1020 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 196 + 144",
        "Answer": "A: 340",
        "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 40 = 130\n200 + 130 = 330\n330 + 4 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 660 + 993",
        "Answer": "A: 1653",
        "Explanation": "600 + 900 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 782 + 846",
        "Answer": "A: 1628",
        "Explanation": "700 + 800 = 1500  \n80 + 40 = 120  \n2 + 6 = 8  \n1500 + 120 = 1620  \n1620 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 361 + 713",
        "Answer": "A: 1074",
        "Explanation": "300 + 700 = 1000\n60 + 10 = 70\n1 + 3 = 4\n1000 + 70 = 1070\n1070 + 4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 623 + 103",
        "Answer": "A: 726",
        "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n20 + 3 = 23\n700 + 23 = 723\n723 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 185 + 242",
        "Answer": "A: 427",
        "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 5 + 2 = 427"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 845 + 806",
        "Answer": "A: 1651",
        "Explanation": "800 + 800 = 1600\n40 + 6 = 46\n1600 + 46 = 1646\n1646 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 730 + 480",
        "Answer": "A: 1210",
        "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 80 = 110\n1100 + 110"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 732 + 472",
        "Answer": "A: 1204",
        "Explanation": "700 + 400 = 1100\n30 + 70 = 100\n2 + 2 = 4\n1100 + 100 = 1200\n1200 + 4"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 142 + 559",
        "Answer": "A: 701",
        "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n40 + 50 = 90\n600 + 90 = 690\n690 + 2 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 622 + 237",
        "Answer": "A: 859",
        "Explanation": "600 + 200 = 800\n20 + 30 = 50\n800 + 50 = 850\n850 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 564 + 743",
        "Answer": "A: 1307",
        "Explanation": "500 + 700 = 1200\n60 + 40 = 100\n1200 + 100 = 1300\n1300 + 3 = 1303\n1303 +"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 883 + 696",
        "Answer": "A: 1579",
        "Explanation": "800 + 600 = 1400\n80 + 90 = 170\n1400 + 170 = 1570\n1570 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 761 + 297",
        "Answer": "A: 1058",
        "Explanation": "700 + 200 = 900  \n60 + 90 = 150  \n900 + 150 = 1050  \n1050 + 8"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 637 + 439",
        "Answer": "A: 1076",
        "Explanation": "600 + 400 = 1000\n30 + 30 = 60\n7 + 9 = 16\n1000 + 60 = 1060\n1060 + 16"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 180 + 567",
        "Answer": "A: 747",
        "Explanation": "100 + 500 = 600\n80 + 60 = 140\n600 + 140 = 740\n740 + 7"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 243 + 749",
        "Answer": "A: 992",
        "Explanation": "200 + 700 = 900\n40 + 40 = 80\n900 + 80 = 980\n980 + 3 + 9"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 904 + 241",
        "Answer": "A: 1145",
        "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n4 + 40 = 44  \n1100 + 44 = 1144  \n1144 + 1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 422 + 682",
        "Answer": "A: 1104",
        "Explanation": "400 + 600 = 1000\n20 + 80 = 100\n1000 + 100 = 1100\n1100 + 2\n1100 + 2 = "
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 195 + 121",
        "Answer": "A: 316",
        "Explanation": "100 + 100 = 200\n90 + 20 = 110\n110 + 5 = 115\n200 + 115 = 315\n315 + 1"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 917 + 340",
        "Answer": "A: 1257",
        "Explanation": "900 + 300 = 1200  \n17 + 40 = 57  \n1200 + 57"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 510 + 470",
        "Answer": "A: 980",
        "Explanation": "500 + 400 = 900\n10 + 70 = 80\n900 + 80"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 924 + 211",
        "Answer": "A: 1135",
        "Explanation": "900 + 200 = 1100  \n20 + 10 = 30  \n1100 + 30 = 1130  \n1130 + 5"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 962 + 693",
        "Answer": "A: 1655",
        "Explanation": "900 + 600 = 1500\n60 + 90 = 150\n1500 + 150 = 1650\n1650 + 2 + 3"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 183 + 249",
        "Answer": "A: 432",
        "Explanation": "100 + 200 = 300\n80 + 40 = 120\n3 + 9 = 12\n300 + 120 = 420\n420 + 12"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 632 + 186",
        "Answer": "A: 818",
        "Explanation": "600 + 100 = 700\n30 + 80 = 110\n700 + 110 = 810\n810 + 8 = 818\n818 + 6"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Q: 787 + 553",
        "Answer": "A: 1340",
        "Explanation": "700 + 500 = 1200\n80 + 50 = 130\n1200 + 130 = 1330\n1330 + 10 = 1340"
    }
]